https://www.golfvacationsuk.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Golf Vacations UK Privacy Policy Details   Golf Vacations UK respects your privacy. We understand your desire to keep your personal information private. In an effort to communicate our understanding of your privacy rights, we have drafted the following Privacy Policy. Read through the details carefully. Discover how we protect your privacy. This privacy policy is about the way information collected is used. No personal information is collected however information is collected about how users access and use this website. 1. The information collected and used If you use this website, you are in control of what information is collected, but if you choose not to share your information, you may not be able to access or use some areas of this website. 1a. How information is collected This information may be collected, stored and used when you use this website and when you call the Advertiser. 1b. What information is collected The information collected and held may include but is not limited to: • information about your computer and about your visits to, and use of, the website (including your IP address, approximate geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views); • if you call the Advertiser, your phone and/or mobile phone number and the time, date and day of the week and length of your call; and • any other information you may provide to the provider of this site. 1c. Using cookies or other on-device storage Cookies are information files stored on your computer that help websites remember you. Cookies are used on this site to collect information. For more information on how use cookies and how to opt out of using them, please read section 6 – the use of Cookies on this website and how you can reject them. 2. How information collected is used 2a. When you use this website When you use this website, information is collected. It will be used for the purposes set out in this privacy policy. 2b. Customisation of this website and advert targeting The information collected when you use this website may be used to build up a picture of your interests. This information may be used to try to make sure that when you visit or use the website, you don’t miss offers and information that might interest you. This is called advert targeting. 2c. Tracking how the website is used Information may be collected about activity on the website, or other organisations may be used to collect it and to share it. This information is used to: • analyse statistics; • track pages and paths used by visitors to, or users of, the website; • target the adverts or offers, such as banners, on the website and on the websites of other organisations; and • track the use of the internet banner adverts and other links from marketing partners’ websites to the website. For these purposes, the information on the path you take to get to the website and on some of the pages you visit or use through the website, using cookies, web beacons and other on-device storage will be retained. You cannot be personally identified from the information that is collected on this website. For information about web beacons, or the organisation used (including how to decline their cookies), please read section 6 – Using cookies on this website and how you can reject them. 2d. Analysing call volumes If you call the Advertiser using the number featured on the website, we will record your phone number, the time, date, day of the week and length of the call and certain details about whether the call was answered or not. This information will be shared with the Advertiser and used it to analyse the effectiveness of the website. Disclosure ofyour information Your information may be passed to one or more of the following organisations: • the Advertiser; • data processing companies, mailing houses and other third party suppliers; and • government and enforcement agencies and the police. Occasionally, this may involve sending your information outside the European Economic Area. For more information, please read section 4 – Where your information is processed. Every now and again, requests are received for information from government departments, the police and other enforcement agencies. If this happens, and there is a proper legal basis for providing your information, it will be provided to the organisation asking for it. 4. Where your information is processed When your information is used as described in section 2 – How information collected is used, this may occasionally involve sending your information outside the European Economic Area (EEA). Where this is done, appropriate steps are taken to protect your information. By using this website, you agree that your information may be transferred, stored and processed outside the EEA. 5. How your information secure is kept secure The security of information is taken very seriously. Technology and security policies are in place to protect the information held. 6. Using cookies on the website and how you can reject them A cookie is a piece of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer’s hard disk so that the website can remember who you are and information about your visit. Cookies can help to display the information on a website in a way that matches your interests. Most major websites use cookies. Two types of cookies are used on this website. The first type is a ‘session-based’ cookie. This means that it is only saved on your hard disk for the time you are using the website. Within the website these cookies are used to understand how users navigate through the web site. The second type of cookie used stays on your hard disk for up to five years. This ‘persistent’ cookie helps the number of different people coming to the site be understood, rather than the total number of times the site is used. Without the persistent cookie, if you visited the site once each week for three weeks you would be counted as three separate users. On the website, these cookies are used to manage the adverts shown to visitors and to make sure that each visitor doesn’t see the same advert too often, as well as understand how frequently you use the website and any services provided on the website. Your personal information is not stored in either type of cookie. Cookies are only used to analyse the effectiveness of the website and to help make the website better for users. If you do not want a website to create a cookie on your computer, most web browsers provide the option to disable them. However, the website may not work properly if you reject the cookies. If you want to know more about how cookies work and how to manage or delete them, visit the World Wide Web Consortium’s website or visit the Interactive Advertising Bureau’s website. Web beacons A web beacon – sometimes called a clear GIF (Graphics Interchange Format) or page tag – is an invisible image file installed on some of the pages. When your computer downloads this image, some information about the page that you and your computer are viewing is recorded. The information does not identify you (for example, it does not include your name or email address)….Web beacons help provide a better service to you by allowing an understanding of which areas of the site are more popular with visitors than others. Web beacons are not used to collect any personal information about you, but they allow a build up of general information about how people use this site. Certain pages on the website may also contain web beacons put in place by the advertising agencies so that a measure can be made of how useful the advertising is on other websites. Web beacon files let the agency recognise a unique cookie on your web browser, which in turn means a learning of which adverts bring users to the website. The web beacon only records a limited amount of information that includes the cookie number, the page ID and the time and date you accessed the page. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number or email address. 7. How changes to this privacy policy may occur This privacy policy may be updated from time to time so you may want to check it each time you visit the website.
Contact Us
Please contact for more information US and Canada TOLL FREE: 888 209 4094 OTHER COUNTRIES: 44 (0) 1228 598089 or E-MAIL via our contact form HERE
